[
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   1 ?",
    "answer":"Evet"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu  2   ?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   3  ?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   4  ?",
    "answer":"Evet"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu  2   ?",
    "answer":"Evet"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   3  ?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   4  ?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  }
,
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   1 ?",
    "answer":"Evet"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu  2   ?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   3  ?",
    "answer":"Hayır"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   4  ?",
    "answer":"Evet"
  }




]
